<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Created using XmlSitemapGenerator.org - Free HTML, RSS and XML sitemap generator-->
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title> 
            
            MGM
            SINCE 1963.
             Mar Gregorios Memorial 
            
            </title>
    <link>http://mgmkottayam.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <guid>http://mgmkottayam.com/</guid>
      <title> 
            
            MGM
            SINCE 1963.
             Mar Gregorios Memorial 
            
            </title>
      <link>http://mgmkottayam.com/</link>
      <description>MGM is one of the fast-growing group of health care industries with more customer centric services. We guarantee Quality, Convenience, and Value which defines who we are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>http://mgmkottayam.com/lodge.html</guid>
      <title>MGM LODGING KOTTAYAM</title>
      <link>http://mgmkottayam.com/lodge.html</link>
      <description>MGM Lodging Services is at Kottayam Town with range of view to pioneer and to serve people in a better way and make them happy and build a trustful relationship with them. We cater your basic needs along with comfortable stay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>http://mgmkottayam.com/eyecare.html</guid>
      <title>COMING SOON!!!!!</title>
      <link>http://mgmkottayam.com/eyecare.html</link>
      <description>MGM Eye Care is a great source for authentic vintage &amp;amp; antique eyeglasses. We have pioneered the evolution of eye wear from functional products to a luxury fashion accessory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>http://mgmkottayam.com/laboratory.html</guid>
      <title>MGM X-RAY &amp;amp; CLINICAL LABORATORY KOTTAYAM</title>
      <link>http://mgmkottayam.com/laboratory.html</link>
      <description>We provide qualitative and quantitative analysis of biological and aspirated fluids such as blood, serum or plasma, tissue, urine, stool, C.S.F. etc. We also ensure diagnostic medical imaging services such as digital X-Ray with enhanced images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>http://mgmkottayam.com/institute.html</guid>
      <title>MGM Paramedical Institute</title>
      <link>http://mgmkottayam.com/institute.html</link>
      <description>We deliver high quality and integrated medical education for
bringing out skilled and disciplined paramedics in Kottayam District with
the experience more than five decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>http://mgmkottayam.com/medicals.html</guid>
      <title>MGM MEDICALS KOTTAYAM</title>
      <link>http://mgmkottayam.com/medicals.html</link>
      <description>MGM Medicals started as the fulfillment of a dream nurtured deep in the heart to the express purpose of making it safer, convenient &amp;amp; affordable for consumers to purchase medicines and continues its legacy of 17 years of success in the pharmaceutical industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>http://mgmkottayam.com/forms/register-form.html</guid>
      <title>REGISTRATION FORM</title>
      <link>http://mgmkottayam.com/forms/register-form.html</link>
      <description />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
<!--<guid value="bf5ca2bc-eae1-4ec9-b8d2-204c825c0842" />-->
<!--Created using XmlSitemapGenerator.org - Free HTML, RSS and XML sitemap generator-->